Finding Aid for William D. Ford Papers 1955-1995
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Subject Files 1965-1995, 79 linear feet
  - 1971-1972
    - Congress (Box 10)
    - Congressional Record Inserts (Box 10)
    - Consumer Bulletins (Box 10)
    - Corps of Engineers (Box 10)
    - Crank File (Box 10)
    - Defense Department (Box 10)
    - Democrats (Box 10)
    - Detroit (Box 10)
    - Drug Abuse (Box 10)
    - Education (Box 10)
    - Employment Assistance (Box 10)
    - Environmental Protection Agency (Box 10)
    - FACE [Finance All Children's Education] (Box 10)
    - Federal Aviation Agency (Box 10)
    - Federal Communications Commission (Box 10)
    - Federal Housing Administration-Detroit Loan Scandal (Box 10)
    - Federal Trade Commission (Box 10)
    - Focus: HOPE (Box 10)
    - Food and Drug Administration (Box 10)
    - Foreign Affairs (Box 10)
    - Foster Grandparents Program (Box 10)
    - Great Lakes (Box 10)
    - Hatch Act (Box 10)
    - Health, Education and Welfare, Department of (Box 10)
    - Housing and Urban Development, Department of (Box 10)
    - Interior Department (Box 10)
    - Internal Revenue Service (Box 10)
    - Labor Relations (Box 10)
    - Law Review Article (Box 10)
    - Michigan Carpentry Contractors (Box 11)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence (Box 11)
    - National Education Association (Box 11)
    - Newsletter Responses (Box 11)
    - Nixon (Box 11)
    - Office Administration (Box 11)
    - Phosphates in Detergents (Box 11)
    - Point Mouillee (Box 11)
    - Pollution (Box 11)
    - Post Office (Box 11)
    - POW/MIA Families for Immediate Release (Box 11)
    - Press Party (Box 11)
    - Prisoners of War (Box 11)
    - Public Health Service Closings (Box 11)
    - Public Interest Research Group in Michigan [PIRGIM] (Box 11)
    - Questionnaires (Box 11)
    - Questionnaires, cont. (Box 12)
    - Referred to Private Attorney (Box 12)
    - Response Form Letters (Box 12)
    - River Rouge (Box 12)
    - Senior Citizens (Box 12)
    - Seniority (Box 12)
    - Space (Box 12)
    - Student Assistance (Box 12)
    - Tax Reform (Box 12)
    - Transportation Department (Box 12)
    - Treasury Department (Box 12)
    - Unemployment (Box 12)
    - United Auto Workers (Box 12)
    - United Farm Workers (Box 12)
    - United Nations (Box 12)
    - Urban Problems (Box 12)
    - Urban Renewal (Box 12)
    - Vietnam (Box 12)
    - Voters (Box 12)
    - Wage and Price Control (Box 12)
    - Wallace Campaign (Box 12)
    - Welfare (Box 12)
    - Willow Run Airport (Box 12)
    - Youth Conservation Corps (Box 12)
    - Youth For Understanding (Box 12)
    - Youth Politics Institute (Box 12)
  - 1972-1973
    - Abortion (Box 12)
    - Agricultural Labor Subcommittee (Box 12)
    - Air Force (Box 12)
    - Alaskan Pipeline (Box 12)
    - Amnesty (Box 12)
    - Architect of the Capitol (Box 12)
    - Birthday Picnic [fundraiser] (Box 12)
    - Budget, Federal (Box 12)
    - Busing (Box 12)
    - Cambodia (Box 12)
    - Child Abuse (Box 12)
    - Civil Service Jobs (Box 12)
    - Common Cause (Box 13)
    - Congressional Record Inserts (Box 13)
    - Congressional Reform (Box 13)
    - Cosigned Letters (Box 13)
    - Cost of Living Council (Box 13)
    - Crank File (Box 13)
    - Crime (Box 13)
    - Day Care (Box 13)
    - Democratic Party (Box 13)
    - Detroit Metropolitan Airport (Box 13)
    - Drug Abuse (Box 13)
    - Economy (Box 13)
    - Education (Box 13)
    - Electoral Reform (Box 13)
    - Energy Crisis (Box 13)
    - Environment (Box 13)
    - Environmental Protection Agency (Box 13)
    - Federal Communications Commission (Box 13)
    - Food Prices (Box 13)
    - Food Stamps (Box 13)
    - Foreign Affairs (Box 13)
    - International Joint Commission on Great Lakes Water Levels (Box 13)
    - Gun Control (Box 13)
    - Halloween (Box 13)
    - Health Care (Box 13)
    - Health, Education and Welfare, Department of (Box 13)
    - Health Security (Box 13)
    - Hearings (Box 13)
    - Highway Trust Fund (Box 13)
    - Housing and Urban Development, Department of (Box 13)
    - Israel-Arab War (Box 13)
    - Labor Department (Box 13)
    - Manpower (Box 13)
    - Meat Bill (Box 13)
    - Michigan Governor's Office (Box 13)
    - Minimum Wage (Box 13)
    - Miscellaneous Constituent Correspondence (Box 13)
    - New Detroit (Box 14)
    - Nixon (Box 14)
    - Office Administration (Box 14)
    - Office of Economic Opportunity (Box 14)
    - Pension Protection (Box 14)
    - Pointe Mouillee Marsh (Box 14)
    - Postal Service (Box 14)
    - POW/MIA Families for Immediate Release (Box 14)
    - Prisoners of War (Box 14)
    - Questionnaire Replies (Box 14)
    - Railroads (Box 14)
    - Senior Citizens (Box 14)
    - Social Security (Box 14)
    - State Department (Box 14)
    - Super Sewer (Box 14)
    - Tax Reform (Box 14)
    - Vietnam (Box 14)
    - Watergate (Box 14)
    - Welfare (Box 14)
  - 1973-1974
    - Abortion (Box 14)
    - Air Force (Box 14)
    - Airlines (Box 14)
    - Amnesty (Box 14)
    - Army (Box 14)
    - Auto Regulations (Box 14)
    - Automotive Safety (Box 14)
    - Bolling Report (Box 14)
    - Budget, Federal (Box 14)
    - Campaign Spending and Reform (Box 14)
    - Capital Punishment (Box 14)
    - Committee on Committees (Box 15)
    - Common Cause (Box 15)
    - Communications (Box 15)
    - Congressional Pay Raise (Box 15)
    - Congressional Record Inserts (Box 15)
    - Crank File (Box 15)
    - Cyprus (Box 15)
    - Day Care (Box 15)
    - Democrats, 15th District (Box 15)
    - Detroit Metro Postal Facility (Box 15)
    - Elementary and Secondary Education Amendments [ESEA] (Box 15)
    - Economy (Box 15)
    - Ecorse Creek (Box 15)
    - Education (Box 15)
    - Election Reform (Box 15)
    - Energy Crisis (Box 15)
    - Environment (Box 15)
    - Equal Rights Amendment (Box 15)
    - Extension of Remarks (Box 15)
    - Federal Aviation Agency (Box 15)
    - Flood Control (Box 15)
    - Gas Rationing (Box 15)
    - Great Lakes (Box 15)
    - Gun Control (Box 15)
    - Health Care (Box 15)
    - Health, Education and Welfare, Department of (Box 15)
    - Health Security (Box 15)
    - Highway Safety (Box 15)
    - Hospitals (Box 15)
    - Housing (Box 15)
    - Housing and Urban Development, Department of (Box 15)
    - Impeachment (Box 15)
    - Impounding Funds (Box 15)
    - Indians (Box 15)
    - Inflation (Box 15)
    - Interior Department (Box 15)
    - International Labor Organization (Box 15)
    - Interns (Box 15)
    - Lake Survey Center (Box 16)
    - Layoffs (Box 16)
    - Libraries (Box 16)
    - Miscellaneous Constituent Correspondence (Box 16)
    - Missing In Action (Box 16)
    - Mobile Homes (Box 16)
    - Multiple Sclerosis (Box 16)
    - NASA (Box 16)
    - National Spending Priorities (Box 16)
    - Nike Site (Box 16)
    - Nixon (Box 16)
    - No-Fault Insurance (Box 16)
    - Northwest Orient Airlines (Box 16)
    - Oil Companies (Box 16)
    - Older Americans (Box 16)
    - Pensions (Box 16)
    - Pornography (Box 16)
    - Postal Service (Box 16)
    - Prisoners of War (Box 16)
    - Questionnaire Replies (Box 16)
    - Revenue Sharing (Box 16)
    - Rockefeller Nomination (Box 16)
    - Sex Education (Box 16)
    - Senior Citizens (Box 16)
    - Shaw College (Box 16)
    - Small Business (Box 16)
    - Social Security (Box 16)
    - Statements by Ford (Box 16)
    - Surtax (Box 16)
    - Tax Reform (Box 16)
    - Transportation Regulations (Box 16)
    - Two Dollar Bill (Box 16)
    - United Auto Workers (Box 16)
    - United Nations (Box 16)
    - Wage and Price Controls (Box 16)
    - Watergate (Box 16)
    - Welfare (Box 16)
  - 1974-1975
    - Abortion (Box 16)
    - Action Volunteer Program (Box 16)
    - American Federation of Government Employees (Box 16)
    - American Postal Workers Union (Box 16)
    - Amnesty (Box 16)
    - Amtrak (Box 16)
    - Animal Welfare (Box 16)
    - Arabs (Box 16)
    - Auto Emission Standards (Box 16)
    - Auto Industry (Box 16)
    - Auto Safety (Box 16)
    - B-1 Bomber (Box 17)
    - Belleville Community Hospital (Box 17)
    - Birch Barks (Box 17)
    - Birthday Picnic Fundraiser (Box 17)
    - Budget Committee Appropriations (Box 17)
    - Canning Lids (Box 17)
    - Capital Punishment (Box 17)
    - Central Intelligence Agency (Box 17)
    - Comprehensive Employment and Training Act [CETA] (Box 17)
    - Common Cause (Box 17)
    - Community Services (Box 17)
    - Congress (Box 17)
    - Congressional Record Inserts (Box 17)
    - Consumer Protection Agency (Box 17)
    - Consumers (Box 17)
    - Consumers Power Agency (Box 17)
    - Corps of Engineers (Box 17)
    - Co-signed Letters and Petitions (Box 17)
    - Crank File (Box 17)
    - Crime (Box 17)
    - Dearborn-Dearborn Heights Merger (Box 17)
    - Defense Department (Box 17)
    - Democrats (Box 17)
    - Detente (Box 17)
    - Detroit (Box 17)
    - Detroit Metropolitan Airport (Box 17)
    - Detroit Plan, Inc. (Box 17)
    - Economy (Box 17)
    - Ecorse Creek (Box 17)
    - Education (Box 17)
    - Emergency School Aid Act (Box 17)
    - Energy Crisis (Box 17)
    - Environment (Box 17)
    - Environmental Protection Agency (Box 17)
    - Equal Rights Amendment (Box 17)
    - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission (Box 17)
    - Ethnic Groups (Box 17)
    - Extension of Remarks (Box 17)
    - Federal Communications Commission (Box 17)
    - Federal Energy Office (Box 17)
    - Federal Highway Administration (Box 17)
    - Federal Highway Trust Fund (Box 17)
    - Federal Pay Raise (Box 17)
    - Flood Control (Box 18)
    - Food and Drug Administration (Box 18)
    - Food and Resource Crisis (Box 18)
    - Food Stamps (Box 18)
    - Ford Motor Company (Box 18)
    - Ford, William-personal (Box 18)
    - Foreign Affairs (Box 18)
    - Government Spending (Box 18)
    - Gun Control (Box 18)
    - Health, Education and Welfare, Department of (Box 18)
    - Health Security (Box 18)
    - Highway Safety (Box 18)
    - Housing (Box 18)
    - Housing and Urban Development, Department of (Box 18)
    - Inflation (Box 18)
    - Internal Security Committee (Box 18)
    - Internal Revenue Service (Box 18)
    - Interior Department (Box 18)
    - Kennedy Assassination (Box 18)
    - Labor Department (Box 18)
    - Labor Unions (Box 18)
    - Law Enforcement Assistance Administration (Box 18)
    - League of Women Voters (Box 18)
    - Lotteries (Box 18)
    - "Man-A Course of Study" [MACOS] curriculum (Box 18)
    - Mass Transit (Box 18)
    - Medical Care (Box 18)
    - Medical Research (Box 18)
    - Mental Health (Box 18)
    - MIAs (Box 18)
    - Michigan Department of Natural Resources (Box 18)
    - Michigan Governor's Office (Box 18)
    - Michigan Municipal League (Box 18)
    - Michigan Pollution (Box 18)
    - Michigan State Government (Box 18)
    - Michigan State University (Box 18)
    - Michigan State Medical Society (Box 18)
    - Michigan United Conservation Clubs (Box 18)
    - Middle East (Box 18)
    - Military Draft (Box 18)
    - Military Spending (Box 18)
    - Miscellaneous Constituent Correspondence (Box 18)
    - National Endowment for the Arts (Box 18)
    - National Right to Work Committee (Box 18)
    - New York City (Box 18)
    - Northwestern Michigan Democrats (Box 18)
    - Nursing Homes (Box 18)
    - Obscenity (Box 18)
    - Office Administration (Box 18)
    - Offices of Legislative Counsel (Box 18)
    - Oil Companies (Box 18)
    - Oil Depletion (Box 18)
    - Oil Prices (Box 18)
    - Older Americans (Box 18)
    - Pensions (Box 18)
    - Political Prisoners (Box 19)
    - Postal Service (Box 19)
    - Propane Services, Inc. (Box 19)
    - Questionnaire Replies (Box 19)
    - Railroads (Box 19)
    - Recession (Box 19)
    - Revenue Sharing (Box 19)
    - Rhodesian Chrome (Box 19)
    - Rockefeller (Box 19)
    - Russian Grain Deal (Box 19)
    - School Lunch Override (Box 19)
    - Small Business (Box 19)
    - Social Security (Box 19)
    - Social Services (Box 19)
    - State Department (Box 19)
    - Statements by Congressman Ford (Box 19)
    - Taxation (Box 19)
    - Trade (Box 19)
    - Unemployment (Box 19)
    - Unemployment Compensation (Box 19)
    - United Farm Workers (Box 19)
    - United Nations (Box 19)
    - United States Labor Party (Box 19)
    - United Steel Workers (Box 19)
    - University of Michigan (Box 19)
    - Utilities (Box 19)
    - Veterans (Box 19)
    - Veto (Box 19)
    - Vietnam (Box 19)
    - Wayne State University (Box 19)
    - Welfare (Box 19)
  - 1975-1976
    - Abortion (Box 19)
    - Air Transport Workers Union (Box 19)
    - Animal Welfare (Box 19)
    - Angola (Box 19)
    - Arab Boycott (Box 19)
    - Auto Emission Standards (Box 19)
    - B-1 Bomber (Box 19)
    - Birch Barks (Box 19)
    - Birthday Picnic (Box 19)
    - Busing (Box 19)
    - Capital Punishment (Box 20)
    - Central Intelligence Agency (Box 20)
    - Comprehensive Employment and Training Act [CETA] (Box 20)
    - Congressional Box Scores (Box 20)
    - Conference of Great Lakes Congressmen (Box 20)
    - Congressional Record Inserts (Box 20)
    - Congressional Scandals (Box 20)
    - Crank File (Box 20)
    - Crime (Box 20)
    - Declaration of Independence (Box 20)
    - Democratic Party (Box 20)
    - Detente (Box 20)
    - Disaster Assistance (Box 20)
    - Drug Abuse (Box 20)
    - Education (Box 20)
    - Energy Crisis (Box 20)
    - Environmental Protection Agency (Box 20)
    - Equal Rights Amendment (Box 20)
    - Extension of Remarks (Box 20)
    - Federal Assistance Information Requests (Box 20)
    - Federal Bureau of Investigation (Box 20)
    - Federal Communications Commission (Box 20)
    - Federal Election Commission (Box 20)
    - Food and Resource Crisis (Box 20)
    - Food Stamps (Box 20)
    - Ford, William, personal (Box 20)
    - Great Lakes (Box 20)
    - Gun Control (Box 20)
    - Handicapped (Box 20)
    - Health Care (Box 20)
    - Health, Education and Welfare, Department of (Box 20)
    - Health Security (Box 20)
    - Holder-in-due-course Rule (Box 20)
    - Housing and Urban Development, Department of (Box 20)
    - Illegal Aliens (Box 20)
    - Immigration and Naturalization (Box 20)
    - Indians (Box 20)
    - Jeff-Jack Dinner (Box 20)
    - Kinchloe Air Force Base (Box 20)
    - Lake Survey Center Closing (Box 20)
    - Law Enforcement Assistance Administration (Box 20)
    - Libraries (Box 20)
    - Medicare (Box 20)
    - MIAs (Box 20)
    - Military Spending (Box 20)
    - Municipal Conference (Box 20)
    - Natural Gas (Box 21)
    - Newsletter Responses (Box 21)
    - No-Fault Insurance (Box 21)
    - Nursing Homes (Box 21)
    - Office Administration (Box 21)
    - Oil Prices (Box 21)
    - Peoples Community Hospital Authority (Box 21)
    - Political Prisoners (Box 21)
    - Postal Service (Box 21)
    - Privacy (Box 21)
    - Questionnaire Replies (Box 21)
    - Railroads (Box 21)
    - Rape (Box 21)
    - Recycling (Box 21)
    - Regulatory Agencies (Box 21)
    - Representative Wayne Hays (Box 21)
    - Revenue Sharing (Box 21)
    - Seafarer Project (Box 21)
    - Senior Citizens Tax Deduction (Box 21)
    - Social Security (Box 21)
    - Solar Energy (Box 21)
    - Super Sewer (Box 21)
    - Tax Reform (Box 21)
    - Taylor Handicapped Children's Association (Box 21)
    - Unemployment (Box 21)
    - Veterans Benefits (Box 21)
    - Wayne County (Box 21)
    - Welfare (Box 21)
  - 1976-1977
    - Abortion (Box 21)
    - Airbags (Box 21)
    - Airlines (Box 21)
    - Alaska Pipeline (Box 21)
    - Alcohol Abuse (Box 21)
    - Amnesty (Box 21)
    - Armed Services (Box 21)
    - Asbestos (Box 22)
    - Assassination Committee (Box 22)
    - Auto Emission Standards (Box 22)
    - Auto Safety (Box 22)
    - B-1 Bomber (Box 22)
    - Belleville Lake (Box 22)
    - Bottle Bill (Box 22)
    - Busing (Box 22)
    - Cancer Research (Box 22)
    - Capital Punishment (Box 22)
    - Citizens for Decency (Box 22)
    - Clinch River Breeder Reactor (Box 22)
    - Common Cause (Box 22)
    - Comprehensive Employment and Training Act [CETA] (Box 22)
    - Conference of Great Lakes Congressmen (Box 22)
    - Congressional Luxuries (Box 22)
    - Congressional Record Inserts (Box 22)
    - Crank File (Box 22)
    - Crime (Box 22)
    - Democrats (Box 22)
    - Detroit Metropolitan Airport (Box 22)
    - Detroit Osteopathic Hospital (Box 22)
    - Diabetes (Box 22)
    - Economic Growth Council of Detroit (Box 22)
    - Economy (Box 22)
    - Election Results (Box 22)
    - Energy Crisis (Box 22)
    - Federal Pay Raise (Box 22)
    - Food and Resource Crisis (Box 22)
    - Food Stamps (Box 22)
    - Gun Control (Box 22)
    - Handicapped (Box 22)
    - Hospitals (Box 22)
    - Housing and Urban Development, Department of (Box 22)
    - Hyde Amendment (Box 22)
    - Illegal Aliens (Box 22)
    - Insurance (Box 22)
    - Jesus Movies (Box 22)
    - Law Enforcement Assistance Administration (Box 22)
    - Marijuana (Box 22)
    - McNeil Lehrer Report (Box 22)
    - Medical Schools (Box 22)
    - Michigan Machinists Council (Box 22)
    - Minimum Wage (Box 22)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 22)
    - New Detroit (Box 22)
    - No-Fault Insurance (Box 22)
    - Pages (Box 22)
    - Peoples Community Hospital Authority (Box 22)
    - Pollution (Box 22)
    - Pornography (Box 22)
    - Postal Service (Box 22)
    - Questionnaire Replies (Box 23)
    - Recreation (Box 23)
    - Religious Discrimination (Box 23)
    - Saccharin (Box 23)
    - School Officials Conference (Box 23)
    - Senate 1978 (Box 23)
    - Senior Citizens (Box 23)
    - Staff Information (Box 23)
    - State Department (Box 23)
    - Steel Industry (Box 23)
    - Super Sewer (Box 23)
    - Unemployment (Box 23)
    - Veterans Administration (Box 23)
    - Wayne County General Hospital (Box 23)
    - Welfare (Box 23)
    - Women (Box 23)
  - 1977-1978
    - Abortion (Box 23)
    - Agriculture (Box 23)
    - Alcohol Abuse (Box 23)
    - American Federation of Teachers (Box 23)
    - Armed Services (Box 23)
    - Arthritis (Box 23)
    - Auto Emission Standards (Box 23)
    - Belleville Community Hospital (Box 23)
    - Belleville Lake (Box 23)
    - Birthday Picnic Fundraiser (Box 23)
    - Bottle Bill (Box 23)
    - Campaign 1978 (Box 23)
    - Campaign Financing (Box 23)
    - Capital Punishment (Box 23)
    - Census Figures (Box 23)
    - Civil Aeronautics Board (Box 23)
    - Civil Defense (Box 23)
    - Civil Rights (Box 23)
    - Civil Service (Box 23)
    - Coal (Box 23)
    - Colleague Letters by W.D. Ford (Box 23)
    - Communications (Box 23)
    - Communications Reform Act (Box 23)
    - Communications Workers of America (Box 23)
    - Comprehensive Employment and Training Act [CETA] (Box 23)
    - Congressional Box Scores (Box 23)
    - Congressional Record Inserts (Box 23)
    - Congressional Scandals (Box 23)
    - Congressman Diggs (Box 23)
    - Conrail (Box 23)
    - Co-signed Letters and Petitions (Box 23)
    - Corps of Engineers (Box 23)
    - Crank File (Box 23)
    - Cyprus (Box 23)
    - Cystic Fibrosis (Box 23)
    - Defense Department (Box 23)
    - Democrats (Box 23)
    - Detroit (Box 23)
    - Detroit Metropolitan Airport (Box 23)
    - Economy (Box 24)
    - Ecorse Creek (Box 24)
    - Electoral College Reform (Box 24)
    - Energy (Box 24)
    - Environmental Protection Agency (Box 24)
    - Equal Rights Amendment (Box 24)
    - Fasteners (Box 24)
    - Federal Communications Commission (Box 24)
    - Federal Programs (Box 24)
    - Fifty-five Mile Per Hour Speed Limit (Box 24)
    - Food and Drug Administration (Box 24)
    - Food and Resource Crisis (Box 24)
    - Focus: HOPE (Box 24)
    - Ford Motor Company (Box 24)
    - Forestry Service (Box 24)
    - General Motors Corporation (Box 24)
    - General Services Administration (Box 24)
    - Government Bureaucracy (Box 24)
    - Government Spending (Box 24)
    - Great Lakes (Box 24)
    - Great Lakes Commission (Box 24)
    - Gun Control (Box 24)
    - Handicapped (Box 24)
    - Health Care (Box 24)
    - Health, Education and Welfare, Department of (Box 24)
    - Hospitals (Box 24)
    - Housing (Box 24)
    - Housing and Urban Development, Department of (Box 24)
    - Hyde Amendment (Box 24)
    - Inflation (Box 24)
    - Interior Department (Box 24)
    - Internal Revenue Service (Box 24)
    - International Thespian Society (Box 24)
    - International Trade Commission (Box 24)
    - Interstate Commerce Commission (Box 24)
    - Irish Congressional Caucus (Box 24)
    - Israel-Arab War (Box 24)
    - Judicial Systems (Box 24)
    - Juvenile Delinquency (Box 24)
    - Labor (Box 24)
    - Labor Department (Box 24)
    - Law Enforcement Assistance (Box 24)
    - Legislature of Michigan (Box 24)
    - Marijuana (Box 24)
    - Marston (Box 24)
    - Medicare (Box 24)
    - Members of Congress (Box 24)
    - Michigan State Government Agencies (Box 24)
    - Middle East (Box 24)
    - Military Draft (Box 24)
    - National Association of Greeting Card Publishers (Box 24)
    - National Health Insurance (Box 24)
    - Navratilova, Martina (Box 24)
    - Newsletter Responses (Box 24)
    - Nuclear Regulatory Commission (Box 24)
    - Nursing (Box 24)
    - Occupational Safety and Health Act [OSHA] (Box 24)
    - Office Administration (Box 24)
    - Older Americans Act (Box 24)
    - Olympic Games (Box 24)
    - Patronage, Federal (Box 24)
    - Pension Reform (Box 24)
    - Population (Box 24)
    - Postal Service (Box 24)
    - Postal Workers Union (Box 24)
    - Press Release (Box 24)
    - PBB [poly-brominated biphenyl] contamination (Box 25)
    - Panama Canal (Box 25)
    - Questionnaire Replies (Box 25)
    - Railroads (Box 25)
    - School Prayer (Box 25)
    - SEMTA [Southeastern Michigan Transportation Authority] (Box 25)
    - Senior Citizens (Box 25)
    - Silent Majority (Box 25)
    - Social Security (Box 25)
    - Steel Industry (Box 25)
    - Subcommittee Press Release (Box 25)
    - Tax Reform (Box 25)
    - Taylor Federation of Teachers (Box 25)
    - Unanswered Mail (Box 25)
    - Unemployment (Box 25)
    - United Auto Workers (Box 25)
    - University of Michigan (Box 25)
    - Veterans Administration (Box 25)
    - Veterans Benefits (Box 25)
    - Wayne County Community College (Box 25)
    - Wayne County, Reuther Long Term Care Facility (Box 25)
    - Welfare (Box 25)
  - 1978-1979
    - Abortion (Box 25)
    - Air Traffic Controllers Organization [PATCO] (Box 25)
    - American Council on Education (Box 25)
    - Animal Welfare (Box 25)
    - Amtrak (Box 25)
    - Auto Emission Standards (Box 25)
    - Boat People (Box 25)
    - Budget, Federal (Box 25)
    - Cambodia (Box 25)
    - Campaign Financing (Box 25)
    - Capital Punishment (Box 25)
    - Child Nutrition (Box 25)
    - Chrysler (Box 25)
    - Comprehensive Employment and Training Act [CETA] (Box 25)
    - Congressional Box Scores (Box 25)
    - Congressional Pay Raise (Box 25)
    - Congressional Record Inserts (Box 25)
    - Congressman Diggs (Box 25)
    - Co-signed Letters and Petitions (Box 25)
    - Constitution (Box 25)
    - Crank File (Box 25)
    - Cults (Box 25)
    - Dear Colleague Letters (Box 26)
    - Defense Spending (Box 26)
    - Democrats (Box 26)
    - Detroit Metropolitan Airport (Box 26)
    - District of Columbia (Box 26)
    - Drinking Age (Box 26)
    - Drug Abuse (Box 26)
    - Drug Industry (Box 26)
    - Electoral College Reform (Box 26)
    - Energy Crisis (Box 26)
    - Environment (Box 26)
    - Environmental Protection Agency (Box 26)
    - Equal Rights Amendment (Box 26)
    - Extension of Remarks (Box 26)
    - Federal Aviation Administration (Box 26)
    - Federal Communications Commission (Box 26)
    - Flood (Box 26)
    - Food and Drug Administration (Box 26)
    - Food and Resource Crisis (Box 26)
    - Foreign Affairs (Box 26)